(忆往昔)
-狼人  -它们的内脏都被掏出来了
- Werewolf? - Their organs was ripped clean out.
-心脏被吃掉  -这儿的人都是狼人吗
- Hearts consumed. - Everyone here's a wolf?
我们这里不用"狼人"那个词
We don't use the "W" Word around here.
撕碎心脏  然后吃掉
Break some hearts, then you eat 'em.
-路西法  -该死的
- Lucifer? - Bloody hell.
穿着小卡的这身皮囊
Donning this...Cass mask?
你好啊  迪恩
Hello, Dean.
真是太...
Just ugh.
迪恩  我们会救回他
Dean, we'll get him back.
我们会救回小卡  我们会杀了魔鬼
We're gonna save Cass, we're gonna ice the devil,
我们会干掉黑暗
and we're gonna shank the Darkness.
没错
Damn right.
死神
Reapers?
还有人死  还有灵魂要收
People are still dying, souls to collect.
杀死那些死期到来的人  我有个名单
You kill everyone whose number's up. I have a list.
无需恐惧死亡
Death is nothing to fear.
你是想寻死吗
What, you got some kind of death wish or something?
是你一直打算英勇就义的
You're the one who's always wanted to go out blaze of glory style.
-你怎么会死  -苔莎  帮个忙
- Why are you dead? - Tessa, I need a favor.
我无法忍受你死
I couldn't live with you dead.
你该走了  迪恩
It's your time to go, Dean.
哪怕拼了老命我也要救你
Now, if it's the last thing I do, I'm gonna save you.
-我叫比莉  -死神比莉吗
- Name's Billie. - The reaper Billie?
我弟弟说你想杀了我们
My brother says you want to kill us.
不
No.
我只是要确保等你们死了
I'm just gonna make sure that when you die...
不会再活过来
...you stay dead.
(如今)
[邪恶力量 第11季第17集]
(48小时前)
你那边怎么样
How's it going over there?
没什么变化
Same.
你呢  有发现吗
And you, anything?
好像有
Yeah, I-I think so.
是吗  阿玛拉  路西法还是上帝之手
Yeah? On Amara, Lucifer, Hand of God?
不是  是桩案子
No, no, it's a -- it's a case.
貌似是狼人
Werewolves looks like.
三个月以来有
Um, a pattern of missing campers --
五个驴友失踪
five in the last three months.
走丢了呗
So they got lost.
巡林员本来也这么想
Well, that's what the rangers thought, too,
但几天前  他们发现了一具尸体
until a couple days ago, when they found a body --
我猜猜  心脏没了
Let me guess -- minus a heart.
对
Yeah.
现在他们改说是动物袭击  但是
Now, they're calling it an animal attack, but...
好吧  我们打电话  叫人去看看
All right, well, we make a call and we put somebody on it.
嗯  可是
Yeah, but...
我们会把他救回来的
We'll get him back.
怎么救
How?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
但我们会想到办法的
But we'll figure it out.
现在  我们得离开这儿
Meantime, we got to get out of here.
清空思绪  这是桩案子
Clear our heads. I mean, this is a case.
我们去做本职工作  去办案吧
Let's do what we do. L-Let's work it.
亲爱的  你还醒着吗
Baby, you still with me?
好了
All right, all right.
迪恩  他们
Hey, Dean, they, uh...
你俩撑住
Okay, just hold tight, you two, okay?
听着  我们得把子弹取出来
All right, listen, we got to get that bullet out of there, okay?
这会很疼的
This is gonna hurt like hell.
给  你可能用得着
Here, might need that.
好了
Okay, okay.
好了  就夹到了  就好了
All right. Almost got it. Almost got it.
就这儿
Right there.
出来啊
Come on, come on!
好了  好了
Okay, there we go. There we go.
看啊
Look at that, huh?
这样吧  我们留着这个
Well, you know what? We got to keep that one.
留个念想
That one's gonna be a little memento.
改日拿来开玩笑
We'll laugh about it some other time.
两位  她情况不太好
Guys? She ain't doing so good.
我没事了
I got it.
-给  -谢谢
- Here. - Thanks.
他杀的那个有钥匙
The one he killed, he's got the key.
好
Good. Okay.
他们是什么
W-What were they?
狼人
Werewolves.
我就说他们是怪物
Told you they were monsters.
是啊  亲爱的  你说对了
That's right, baby. You called it.
我以为狼人晚上才出来
I thought werewolves needed nighttime,
月圆之夜
a full moon?
我们在这儿待了几天了
We've been here for days.
他们随时能变身
These guys, they can change any time.
因为他们可能是纯血的
Yeah, that's 'cause they were probably purebloods.
他们能随时变身
And they can change any time.
随心所欲
Any time they want.
她的手腕感染了
Those wrists -- Those wrists are infected.
我们得处理一下
We got to get something on them, okay?
好
Okay.
你没事吧  你怎么样
How we doing? How we doing, huh?
没事吧
You good, you good?
好了  继续压住  压住
All right, keep pressure on it. Keep pressure.
给
Here you go.
包扎一下
Wrap those up.
这里有固话吗
Is there a landline in here?
你没有手机吗
You don't have a cellphone?
几英里内都没信号
There's no service for miles.
往回走几英里我车那里有信号
I had a signal back at the car a couple miles back.
听我说
Okay, listen to me.
我去找信号
I'm gonna go for a signal, okay?
然后送你去见真正的医生
We're gonna get you to a real doctor.
你不会有事的
You're gonna be just fine.
嗯  我知道
Yeah, no, I know.
好了
Okay.
你和我  在国家公园搭便车
You and me, hitching the national parks.
最棒的蜜月了  是吧
Best honeymoon ever, right?
你没事吧  我以为昨天...
Are you okay? I thought yesterday...
就是被划了几道
Just a couple scratches.
我们也来
Hey, we're coming!
不行
No, no, no, no, no.
不  我们不能留下
Oh, no, we can't stay here,
其他人还在外面呢
not with the others still out there.
其他人
Others?
好吧  听着  我弟弟中了枪
Okay, listen, my brother's been shot.
他不能一个人留下
He can't stay here alone.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
-萨姆  -我没事
- Sam, hey. - I'm fine.
我帮你  搭着我
Let me help. Yeah, right here.
那我们走吧  走
Okay, guess we're going. Let's go. Go.
我以前很会记人的
You know, I used to be good with faces,
但我年纪大了
but it's my age
来这儿的人又多
and the number of folks that come through this place.
我不像以前记得那么准了
I seem to have lost the knack, so...
现如今  40岁以下的人对我来说都一张脸
These days, everybody under 40 looks the same to me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧
All right, look...
我们知道我们找对地方了
we know we're in the right place.
我们在公园外的大地标都找过
We've tried all the big landmarks outside of the park --
警局
the police station, the -- the --
我们住的那家廉价旅馆  这间酒吧
the fleabag motel we're staying in, this bar.
嗯  我们要没人可问了
Yeah, well, we're running out of things to interrogate,
除非你想出去  开始审问树木
unless you want to go outside, start talking to the trees.
好吧
Right.
好吧  那今晚到这儿吧
All right, let's call it a night.
嗯
Right.
结账
Grab the check.
我们早上可以去公园服务部
You know, we can go to Park Services in the morning,
找巡林员谈谈
talk to the rangers.
知道我想到什么了吗
You know what I was thinking?
你们该去地役权小屋看看
You boys should check out one of the easement cabins.
是公园里的私产
It's private property within the park.
为了避税才留着的
It's just held onto for tax purposes,
驴友有时发现这些小屋
so campers stumble on them
能在里面待好几周
and they can hole up in there for weeks.
失踪的人里或许有住在那儿的
Some of your missing could be in one of them.
可以告诉我们小屋都在哪吗
Do you mind, um, showing us about where they are?
当然
Oh, yeah, sure.
这里
Right about there.
这帮助很大
Well, that is a big help.
太棒了  谢谢
That's great. Thank you.
不客气
No problem.
谢谢
Thanks.
小心
Careful.
有信号吗
Anything?
还没有
No, nothing yet.
太阳就要升起来了
The sun's gonna be up pretty soon.
撑住
Come on.
好
Okay.
我就说不该在那间旅馆吃辣椒的
I told you that roadhouse chili was a bad idea.
嗯
Yeah.
过来看啊
Guys, over here.
快看
Hey, look at that.
好
Okay.
好了  看看能不能找到无线电或电话
All right, see if you can find a-a radio or a phone.
有声音吗
Anything?
不好使
No, it's dead.
这儿有火柴
I got matches over here.
我把灯点上
I'm gonna light those up.
没事吧
Okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我们得继续走
We got to keep moving.
至少是能走的人
Those of us who -- who can.
-你说什么  -我...
- What did you say? - I -- Look.
米歇尔虽然状况不好  但她还有一丝希望
Hey, Michelle's real sick, but she's got a chance.
他...在拖我们后腿
Him -- he's slowing us down.
-如果他们发现我们  -我们救了你
- And if they find us -- - We saved you, okay?
我们救了你们两个
We saved both of you.
三条命换一条啊
It's three lives versus one.
迪恩  住手
Dean, stop!
迪恩
Dean...
他说得对
he's right.
你们得走了
You guys need to -- to go.
快走
Move.
去求救  再回来找我
Go find help, come back for me.
不  萨姆  不行
No, Sam! No!
我出去
I'm gonna go outside,
找点木头  给你搭个担架
I'm gonna find some wood, gonna build you a litter,
然后我们把他抬出去
and we are going to carry him the rest of the way.
就几英里而已
It's only a couple of miles.
我以为我们把你们训练好了
I thought we trained you boys up right.
我提醒你们他们要来了
I warned you they were coming,
就差没端在盘子里递上来了
all but served them up to you on a platter.
现在怎么办
Now what?
怎么办
Well...
这儿不能待了
we're burned here.
收拾好他们的烂摊子  然后走人
So clean up their mess and we'll get gone.
放开我
Get off me!
好了  好了  没事
Okay. Okay. Okay.
伙计们
Guys?
去找迪恩
Go find Dean.
离开这里
Get out of here.
求你
Please.
走吧
Go.
你得走了
You got to go.
他不肯丢下你
He won't leave you.
没有他  我们也不能活着走出去
And we won't last out there without him.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
对不起
I'm sorry.
柯宾
Corbin?
他
Is...
他是
Is he...
死了
Dead.
我们得走了
We got to go.
萨姆
Sam?
Sammy?
怎么回事
What happened?
我不知道  他突然就断气了
I-I-I don't know. He just went.
萨姆
Sammy?
-萨姆  -不不不
- Sammy. - No, no, no.
是他们
It's them.
让他们来吧
Let 'em come.
不  什么
No. What?
他想留下
He wants to stay.
不行
No, you can't!
你留下  跟他们打  你就死定了
You stay, you fight, you die.
我们也会死的
And so do we.
听着
Look...
他已经死了
he's gone.
很抱歉  但他已经死了
I'm sorry, but he's gone.
救救我们吧
Help us.
求你
Please.
我会回来找你的  好吗
I'm gonna come back for you, okay?
我保证
I promise.
好吧
Okay.
我们走
Let's go.
该死
Damn it!
好吧  如果我们往那边走
All right, so, I think if we head in that way,
走四英里应该就能到小屋
should be about a four-mile trek to the cabin.
我们一直说要休息一下  去宿营
You know, we always talk about taking a break, going camping.
可以把这当宿营  很好玩的
This could be like camping. It could be fun.
哪里好玩了
Yeah, which part?
为了条很弱的线索  在林子里冻得蛋疼
Freezing our nuts off in the middle of the woods on a thin lead?
是啊  就是这部分
Yeah, that part.
得了
Oh, come on.
好吧
Okay.
刚刚是怎么回事
What happened back there?
告诉我
Talk to me.
我救了我们
I saved us.
听着  你伤得很重
Look, you're hurt bad and...
我爱你  米歇尔
And I love you, Michelle.
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
我也是没办法
I did what I had to do.
等等
Wait!
这儿
Right here, right here!
好了
Okay.
走吧  伙计们
Come on, guys.
好了  我们走
Okay, here we go.
-天呐  -走吧
- Geez. - Come on.
你们是遇上什么事了
What'd you all get into?
她需要马上进行救治
She needs medical attention right away.
-等等  -不  你照顾好他们就是了
- Hey, hold up. - No, no, just take care of them.
我得回我车上  找我弟弟
I got to get back to my car, back to my brother.
首先  都给我冷静
Hey, first, everyone is gonna settle down
告诉我究竟怎么回事
and tell me what the hell is going on.
警官  我没时间了
Officer, I don't have the time.
给我挤出时间来
You'll make time.
(杨木急救中心)
尽量别动
Don't try to move if you can help it.
你断了几根肋骨  我还没来得及治疗
You got a couple broken ribs I haven't tended to yet.
那大概是
That, and what is probably...
重脑震荡
a nasty concussion.
帮个忙
Hey, do us both a favor.
休息一下
Get some rest.
然后他弟弟
Then his brother...
他弟弟死了
his brother just died.
我们就逃了
And we ran.
那些坏人  他们还在那儿
The bad guys, they're still out there.
是怪物
Monsters.
狼人
Werewolves.
我们也不知道他们是怎么回事
We don't know what their deal was.
只知道那人说了什么
Only what that guy told us.
"那人"  还有他弟弟救了我们
"That guy" saved us, and so did his brother.
谢谢你们配合
Thank you for your time.
你妻子经受了很大折磨
Your wife's been through a lot.
我会给巡林员打个电话
I'll give a call to the rangers,
让他们去小屋和林站看看
have them check out the cabin and the station,
有什么发现我会通知你
then I'll let you know what they find.
好
Okay.
米歇尔
Michelle...
我们活下来了
we made it.
好了  你妻子情况稳定了
Okay, your wife is stable now.
我该给你看看了
Time for me to get a look at you.
我没事
I'm fine.
那得我说了算
I'll be the judge.
不  真的  我没事的
No. Really, I'm -- I'm good.
坐在床上
Have a seat on the bed.
这是怎么弄的
What did this?
你感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
我觉得...
I feel, uh...
很好
...good.
快点  查理  接电话啊
Come on, Charlie, pick up.
快点
Come on.
我能...
Can -- Can I...
当然
Sure.
我只想来看看你怎么样了
I-I just wanted to see how you were doing.
并告诉你
And to tell you th...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你救了我们
You saved our lives and...
我妈妈以前常说
Well, my mom used to say, um...
我那时并不相信  但现在我或许信了
I didn't believe her then, but I-I think I do now.
她以前常说
She used to say...
死亡不是结束
death -- it's not the end.
迪恩
Dean?
-我  -你在干什么
- I, uh... - What are you doing?
我得
I need to...
我有话要跟...
I need to talk to a --
算不上是朋友  更像是
Well, I wouldn't call it a friend, more like a...
一台恐怖疯狂的死亡机器
scary, crazy death machine.
狼人不是这世上唯一的怪物
Werewolves aren't ‭the only monsters out there.
你要怎么跟一台邪恶恐怖的死亡机器说话
How exactly do you talk to an evil, scary death machine?
很简单
Easy.
死掉
I die.
什么
What?
听着  如果你不...
Look, if you don't...
如果你想走  我理解的
If you want to leave, I get it.
但如果你想帮忙
But if you want to help me...
我要找一切名字里带
I'm looking for pretty much anything
"巴比妥"(镇静安眠)的东西
with "barbital" in the name.
嗯
Yeah.
这能成功吗
This will work?
必须成功
It has to.
好了
Okay.
我吞药之后  去叫医生
After I do this, go get the doc
告诉她
and tell her to, um...
叫她尽量把我救活
Tell her to bring me back, if she can.
如果不行
If not...
也别自责
no hard feelings, okay?
你不非得这么做的
You don't have to do this.
我必须做
Yeah, I do.
迪恩
Dean?
去那边看看
Go around that side.
你感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
迪恩
Dean?
在这边
It's in here.
他服了什么
What did he take?
该死  给我拿纳洛酮(吗啡拮抗药)来
Damn it. Uh, grab me naloxone.
是个小瓶子  中间架上  还有一袋盐水
It's the little bottle, middle shelf, and a bag of saline.
我们得给他注射
We need to run a line.
该死
Damn it.
按住他
Hold him down.
-按抓他  -我在使劲了
- Hold him! - I'm trying!
-帮帮忙  -老天爷
- Help! - Holy hell.
帮帮我们
Help us!
把我放躺  那样更容易找血管
Put me on my back. ‭It's easier to find a vein.
不  把他翻过去
No. Roll him over.
我按住他了
I got him.
可算来了
Well, it took you long enough.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
为什么定格了
What's with the freeze-frame?
在享受这一刻
Just savoring this.
不过我得说  我想象过你很多死法
Though I have to say of all the ways I thought you'd go --
心脏病  被尖牙杀掉
heart attack, some fang,
连看《查理当家》时吃汉堡噎死
choking on a burger while binge-watching "Charles in Charge"...
那可是拜奥的经典
Well, that was peak Baio.
重点是  我没想到你是会自杀的人
Point is, never took you for the suicide type.
不符合你的殉道士精神
Doesn't fit your whole martyr thing.
那么
So...
你好吗
'Sup?
我们得谈谈萨姆的事
We need to talk about Sam.
萨姆怎么了
What about Sam?
我需要他回来
I need him back.
-回来  -别耍把戏了
- Back? - Stop playing.
他在你那儿  我需要他  我们做个交易吧
Look, you've got him, I need him. Let's make a deal.
免了
Pass.
不是吧  就这样吗
Really? Just like that?
就这样
Just like that.
黑暗还在外面
You know, the Darkness is out there...
世界会毁灭的
and the world is gonna burn.
如果她得逞了
And once she gets started,
一切都将终结  包括你
that's the end of everything, including you.
萨姆是唯一能阻止的
Now, Sam's the only one who can stop it.
怎么说
How's that?
我猜到了
That's what I thought.
不过真有爱
It's cute, though.
你假装想为大局救萨姆
You pretending you're trying to save Sam for the greater good,
但我们都知道  你不过是为了自己
when we both know you're doing it for you.
你受不了失去他
You can't lose him.
但即便萨姆能打赢
But even if Sammy could win the title bout...
我的答复还是"不"
the answer would still be "No."
永远都是"不"
The answer will always be "No."
结束了  迪恩
Game's over, Dean.
再没有第二次机会了
No more second chances.
没有多一条命了
No more extra lives.
该跟路易吉告别了  马里奥
Time to say bye-bye to Luigi, Mario.
我请求你
I'm asking you...
我恳求你
I'm begging you, please.
让他回来吧
Bring him back.
让他回来  带我走
Bring him back and take me instead.
我不是来跟你讨价还价的  小子
I'm not here to bargain with you, kid.
我是来收你的
I'm here to reap you.
有趣的是
And the kicker is...
萨姆还没死呢
Sam's not dead.
但你死了
But you are.
至少很快就要死了
Or will be, soon enough.
脉搏在衰弱  把心搏托盘给我
Pulse is fading. ‭Throw me that cardio tray.
-怎么会  -相信我
- But how? - Trust me.
如果温家人死了  我肯定会知道
If the big "W" bit it, I'd get a call.
走吧  迪恩
Come along now, Dean.
时间到了
It's time.
好了
Okay.
空虚
The empty...
在等待
it's waiting.
把他翻过去
Turn him on his side.
好了
Okay.
他还活着
He's alive.
-他  -萨姆
- He? - Sam?
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
跟他没啥关系
Yeah, not so much.
我需要辆车
I need a -- I need a car.
不不  绝对不行
No. No, not a chance.
听着  我不是在求你
Look, pal, I'm not asking.
听着  疯子  你盗窃
Hey, look, psycho, I got you for stealing
并吞服剂量足以判重刑的限制药物
and consuming a felony's worth of Schedule IV drugs,
还袭击警官
plus assaulting a police officer.
你哪都别想去  给他打镇静剂
You ain't going nowhere. Sedate him.
不行
No.
我们出去说句话  好吗
Can we have a word outside, please?
他现在最不需要的就是再打药了
More drugs is the last thing he needs.
他会再次没命的
He could die -- again.
好吧  那你盯住他
Fine, just keep your eye on him.
我去呼叫白鸟
I'm gonna call over to White Bird,
叫些支援来
get some backup in here.
萨姆
Sammy?
迪恩  嗯
Dean, yeah.
天呐
Oh, God.
我...怎么回事
I -- What happened?
你在哪
Where are you?
我在54号公路上的急救中心
I'm, uh, at the Urgent Care on 54.
是柯...
Is Cor-- ‭
萨姆
Sammy?
柯宾跟你在一起吗
Is Corbin with you?
萨姆
Sam?!
迪恩
Dean! ‭
有人吗
Hello?
你没事吧
You okay?
我真的没事
I really am.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
怎么回事  出什么事了
What was that? What happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
柯宾
Corbin?
亲爱的
Hey, baby.
求你  别怕我
Please, don't be scared of me.
这不是我想要的
I didn't want this.
这一切都不是
Okay, any of this, but...
但还是发生了  我感觉好...
it's happened and it feels so...
你会明白的
You'll see.
我们能在一起
We'll be together.
不  求你
No. Please.
-永远在一起  -不
- Forever. - No!
跑
Run!
不  不
No! No!
你可算来了
It took you long enough.
你怎么样了
How you doing?
你弟弟怎么样了
How's your brother?
医生说
The doc says that, um...
柯宾憋死萨姆时
Well, when Corbin choked him,
他进入了休克状态
‭Sam's body went into shock
他的呼吸  心跳
and his breathing, his heartbeat
都减弱到几乎无法察觉
slowed down to almost nothing.
所以他只是差点死了
So he was, uh -- ‭he was just mostly dead.
但他不会有事
But he'll be okay.
那很好啊
Must be nice.
那不是
That wasn't...
柯宾不是个杀人犯
Corbin wasn't a killer.
我知道
I know.
他是为了我
He did it for me.
米歇尔  这会很难承受
Michelle, ‭this is gonna be very hard.
但你不会有事的
But you will be okay.
最终
And, eventually...
你能恢复正常
eventually ‭you'll get back to normal.
我不会的
No, I won't.
他们一小时前
They said I could leave...
就说我可以走了
an hour ago.
但是
But...
我该去哪呢
where am I even supposed to go?
我们一起经历了那么多
After everything we survived together...
我还是看着我爱的人死掉
I watched the man I love die.
我再也回不到正常了
There's no normal after that.
就这样啊
So, that's it, huh?
两夸脱O阴型血输进去  你就没事了
Two quarts O-neg, and you're good to go.
她怎么样
How is she?
她很坚强  会没事的
She's strong. She'll be all right.
线缝得结实吗
Those stitches gonna hold?
结实  是专业级别的
Oh, yeah -- uh, professional grade.
用几天抗生素  卧床休息一下
Couple days of antibiotics and some bed rest,
然后我就能恢复正常了
and I'm, uh, back to normal.
你做了什么
Hey, so, what did you do?
你以为我死了的时候
When you thought I was dead?
你都做了什么
What did you do?
我考虑过重新装修你的房间
Thought about redecorating your room,
放个按摩浴缸  迪斯科球
you know, putting in a Jacuzzi, a nice disco ball --
提高地堡的格调
really class up the joint.
别闹了
Right, seriously.
我
What, I, uh...
我知道你没死
I knew you weren't dead.
好吧
Right.
我知道的
I knew.